

# COLLINS IGHOKPO

Digital Marketer | Graphic Designer

**CollinsIghoben** 

(i) Ilinxxdesigns

in CollinsIghoben

# **EXPERIENCES**

**GRAPHIC DESIGNER** FREELANCE GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Freelance Creative and Graphic designer at Feverr where clients 2017 - Present

satisfiation is our top priority...

DIGITAL MARKETING CLICKBANK AND JVZOO AFFILIATE

CB and JVzoo affiliate marketer, creating website and landing to 2014 - Present

generating leads and sales

# **ABOUT ME**

My Name is Collins Ighokpo and I'm a digital marketing expert with wealth of experience, I focuse on my client's need, moving them to their desired goals. Also, I perform my duties effectively and efficiently, I am innovative and I find creative ways to stimulate minds and

ideas around me.

# **EDUCATION**

#### WESTERN DELTA UNIVERSITY BARCHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

Relevant course: Computer Programming, Networking and 2013 - 2017

Graphic Design

PROJECT: Analysis and Evaluation of Selected Programming

2018 - 2019 NATIONAL YOUTH SERVICE PROGRAM (NYSC)

## PERSONAL DATA

SEX: MALE

DATE OF BIRTH: 23rd NOV 1994

MARITAL STATUS: **SINGLE** 

L.G.A: ISOKO SOUTH

STATE OF ORIGIN: **DELTA STATE** 

NATIONALITY: **NIGERIAN** 

# **SKILLS**



## CONTACT

Address:

NO.4 Emeta Close Amawa Layout

Mobile: 08130196394

llinxxdesigns.biz@yahoo.com

Website:

webbiekoala.com